blackcelebkids.com 2019-09-15

# PRIVACY/COPYRIGHT POLICY - BCK Online

Black Celebrity Kids respects the  privacy of our visitors. The following privacy policy covers the website bckonline.com and all services related to this website only. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. “Personally Identifiable Information” is known as any information by which you can be identified,  such as your first and last name, home or other physical address (including street name and name of a city or town), telephone number or e-mail address .

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW IT USED

**Information You Voluntarily Submit** : We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. You may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, submitting a contact form or creating a username and password. 

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible.  To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation.  Your email address will never be made public. You may choose to also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your  own website.You can also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account. Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website, including but not limited to your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions,  and religious beliefs. If you should choose to provide such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Information We Collect from Others** : We may receive information about you from other sources.  You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile.  If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.  

**Automatically-Collected Information** : 

We may use your IP address to analyze trends as well as to track your site movement, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personal data. The IP address, assigned by your Internet service provider (ISP), is stored as this is the only way to prevent the misuse of our services. We may use third-party service providers to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Website. These third-party service providers may use non-personal data (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. This information is collected through the use of pixel tags or cookies.

**Children’s Information**

This website does not collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent and you feel that this website has collected information of your child, please contact us immediately at info@bckonline.com and we will do our best to remove such information from our records. So that we may comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we ask that children under the age of thirteen not provide any personal information on this website.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected in the following ways to identify you as a user of the Website, create an account for you, send newsletters, send technical notices and updates on policies, or security alerts, to respond to inquiries, track and measure advertising.

THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will not sell or share personal data with other people or non-affiliated companies.  We will use your personal data to provide services to you at your request. We may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, or to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

**This Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:**

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

Mail Chimp – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to [Mail Chimp’s privacy policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) for further information.

Getty Images- Getty Images allows the embedding of stock images (where possibly free of charge). Embedding is the inclusion or integration of any specific foreign content, e.g. text, video or image data provided by a foreign website, and then appears on the own website. To display third-party content, the external content is loaded directly from the other Internet site. Getty Images provides further information about the embedded of content under http://www.gettyimages.de/resources/embed.  

SECURITY  
Black Celebrity Kids  has implemented security measures to protect personal data collected through this website. This includes compliance with related U.S. federal regulations and may include use of industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Though we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk.

COOKIES

Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser.

Through the use of cookies, Black Celebrity Kids can provide users of this website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without the cookie setting.  
Cookies make it easier for users to utilize our website. This Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described above.

ADVERTISING

**Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above. 

**Affiliate Program Participation**

This Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

Black Celebrity Kids is a member of Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.  

**Newsletters**

On this website, users are given the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletter.  Our newsletter may only be received by you if you provide a valid e-mail address and name .

You can choose to subscribe to our newsletter at anytime and are not obligated to do so. 

Newsletters sent may or may not contain promotions. It will, however,  contain tracking pixels, which helps us to analyze the success of a online marketing campaigns.We also use the tracking pixel to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. 

You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at [info@bckonline.com](mailto:info@bckonline.com) to be removed from our mailing list.

**GiveAways**

We may operate contests, and similar promotions through the Site. We typically ask you for certain Personally Identifiable Information when you enter and, if applicable, win a sweepstakes, contest, or similar promotion. When you enter a contest or sweepstakes or participate in a survey or poll, we may ask you to provide your name, address, and e-mail address. We use the information we collect on promotion entry forms to enter you into the contest.

We reserve the right to share this Personally Identifiable Information with third party sponsors of such sweepstakes, contests, and promotions.

YOUR RIGHTS

You may review, update, correct, or change the personal data  you have provided to us at anytime. You may also choose to no longer receive any communication from us.

Contact us at info@bckonline.com to amend or update your personal information.

CONTACT INFORMATION

We reserve  the right to change this Policy at any time. We will announce any such change by posting the revised draft of this Policy on the Site.

Contact us at [info@bckonline.com](mailto:info@bckonline.com) for questions related to this Privacy Policy. 

Copyright

Black Celebrity Kids does not claim credit for any images posted on www.bckonline.com that do not bear our watermark. Uncredited images, found in the public domain, are used in accordance with the Fair Use Doctrine, 17 USC Section 107, for purposes of criticism, commentary, news reporting or editorial use.Neither Black Celebrity Kids nor any third party affiliates of ours claim ownership of photos found in the public domain.

**Policy Last Updated 5/30/2018**
